daytum.com 2019-04-18

# DAYTUM

## Information We Gather

The information we gather falls into three categories: 1) personal information you voluntarily supply when you subscribe, post data points, complete fields for data entry, provide your e-mail address, or, in the future if such services become available, register for an online discussion, or enter a contest, 2) credit card or other billing information for subscription services, and 3) tracking information collected as you navigate through our sites.

_USE OF INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE_

• If you have registered online to our site, Daytum will not sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your e-mail address without your permission. This also applies to any information that personally identifies you, except as noted immediately below. We may, however, share information about our audience in aggregate form. For example, we may want to know how long the average reader spends on our site, or which pages or features get the most attention.  
• Daytum may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about our products and services, including but not limited to our Service. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.  
• Daytum may perform statistical analyses of subscribers and their subscribing and site use patterns for product development purposes and to generally inform third parties about the nature of our subscriber base.  
• We contract with other companies to provide services on our behalf, including credit-card and billing processing, e-mail distribution, list processing and analytics.  
• Information you disclose when posting to the website, along with your screen name and photo or image, is public and may be used by Daytum for online and offline promotional or commercial uses in any and all media. Notwithstanding the foregoing, you retain all rights to your data, consistent with the Terms of Use, which shall prevail.  
• Daytum Plus paid subscriptions are available for purchase pursuant to the Terms of Use. Paid Subscribers to the Daytum Plus Premium Services may elect to protect information posted to the website, and that information is not publicly-available, subject to the Terms of Use and other explicit limitations set forth herein.

_PRIVATE POSTING OF INFORMATION_

For Daytum users who are NOT a Member of Daytum Plus, postings of user information, data entries and displays are publicly accessible and there is no limiting who may or may not see your information. You agree and understand that anything that you post under this service will be made available to anyone who visits the Daytum site and may be viewed by the general public.

_Paid Subscribers to Daytum Plus_ : Subscribers to Daytum Plus Premium Services pay to have the right to restrict authorized public access to their data entries and displays. IF A DAYTUM PLUS SUBSCRIBER RESCINDS ITS DAYTUM PLUS SUBSCRIPTION, BY CANCELLATION OR BY FAILURE TO MAKE PAYMENT, THEN THE PREMIUM SERVICES WILL END. AS A PRACTICAL MATTER, DAYTUM WILL FREEZE THE ACCOUNT, WHICH SHOULD KEEP INFORMATION PRIVATE. HOWEVER, IT IS BEST PRACTICES FOR YOU TO DELETE ANY INFORMATION THAT YOU DO NOT WISH TO BECOME PUBLIC PRIOR TO CANCELLING YOUR SUBSCRIPTION OR ALLOWING SUCH SUBSCRIPTION TO LAPSE as this policy may be subject to change over time. Please note also that, like any website, no security measure is foolproof. If someone, such as a computer hacker, is highly motivated to access your information, they may be able to find a way to access it. They will have likely violated applicable laws such as the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act, and, as such, they will have likely exposed themselves to liability. Daytum makes reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access to the private information of Daytum Plus subscribers, but you acknowledge that there is some risk of posting sensitive private information and you acknowledge that you assume this risk.

## LAST UPDATED: March 10, 2009

_Use of Tracking Information_

_Cookies_ : As is standard practice on many Web sites, Daytum uses “cookies” and other technologies to recognize you and provide personalization, as well as to help us understand which parts of our website are the most popular, where our visitors are going and how much time they spend there. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. Daytum may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our services. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. Users who do not accept cookies from the domain “daytum.com” may not be able to access most all areas of our site.

_Log Data_ : When you visit our site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website; this automatic data collection by our servers is called “log data”. Log data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use log data to monitor the use of the site and of our service, and for the site's technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Use.

_Changing or Deleting Information_

If you are a registered user of the site, you may access and update or correct the information you provided to us on your settings and account pages.

_Our Policy Towards Children_

The site is not directed to persons under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files.

_Links_

Daytum’s website contains links to other sites. Daytum is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy policy applies solely to information directly collected by Daytum.

_Legal Disclaimer_

Daytum may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us, our partners, sponsors, investors, or affiliates; (b) protect and defend our rights or property or those of our users; and (c) act as immediately necessary in order to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

_Business Transfers_

Daytum may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personally identifiable information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity's planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

_Important Information About Policy Changes_

This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on this page. If we make a significant or material change in the way we use your personal information, the change will be posted thirty (30) days prior to taking effect.

_How To Contact Us_

For any questions or comments regarding our information or security practices, you may contact us by e-mail at [feedback@daytum.com](mailto:feedback@daytum.com).
